He promised peace, but chose war.
Path to War is a drama, history, tv movie film directed by John Frankenheimer.
A powerful drama of soaring ambition and shattered dreams that takes a provocative insider's look at the way the
USA goes to war—as seen from inside the LBJ White House leading up to and during the Vietnam War.
Lyndon Johnson, played by Michael Gambon.
Clark Clifford, played by Donald Sutherland.
Robert McNamara, played by Alec Baldwin.
George Ball, played by Bruce McGill.
Richard Goodwin, played by James Frain.
Lady Bird Johnson, played by Felicity Huffman.
Timeline is a 2003 historical science fiction adventure film directed by Richard Donner and starring Paul
Walker, Frances O'Connor, Gerard Butler, Billy Connolly, David Thewlis, and Anna Friel.
Based on Michael Crichton's 1999 novel of the same name, the film concerns a team of present-day archaeology and history
students who are sent back in time to medieval France to rescue their professor from the middle of a battle.
Jerry Goldsmith composed the original score, which would have been his last released before his death in 2004, but was replaced with a new score by
Brian Tyler, after the first cut of the film was re-edited and Goldsmith's increasing health problems prevented him from continuing.
The film was poorly received by critics and bombed at the
box office, losing an estimated $49 million.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, vietcong,
usa president, cold war, failure.
The tone is emotional.